Dean Rodel Legada

Sultan Kudarat, Soccsksargen, Philippines



deanzdeluxe@gmail.com



09757694432



linkedin.com/in/dean-rodel-legada-12b325197

Summary

I'm a Fresh Graduate Full-Stack Web Developer Focusing on Frontend development with good analytical skills. I have experience in developing ecommerce website when I was a student at Zuitt Coding Bootcamp. During which I was able to establish a profound understanding of cutting edge technologies like ReactJS Node.js and engaging from different programming tools. This experience helped me become proactive in problem solving. I am very hungry for learning to enhance my programming skills and reach new heights. And Now that I am a certified Full-Stack Web Developer, I am now on a hunt for a company that will not only consider me as a mere people but an asset that will help boost the company's success in no time. Moreover, I would like to contribute to your organization, enhancing my skills to develop webpage application using available frameworks.

Experience

Student

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp

Apr 2022 - May 2022 (2 months)

Fullstack Web Development

Capstone Project 3 - Ecommerce Webpage

- Create Ecommerce webpage using MERN Stack (JavaScript, MongoDB, Express, ReactJS, NodeJS)
- Create the Frontend Webpage using ReactJS
- Backend API from my Capstone 2 project
- Hosted the Website using Vercel

Student

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp

Mar 2022 - Apr 2022 (2 months)

Backend Web Development

Capstone Project 2 - API for ecommerce webpage

- Creating a NoSQL using MongoDB with the following functionalities:
- · User registration and authentication
- Admin authentication with jwt
- CRUD functions for admin only
- Hosted the application using Heruko

Tools: Javascript, MongoDB, Node.is, Postman, Express.is, Heroku

Student

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp

Feb 2022 - Mar 2022 (2 months)

Front-end Web Development

Capstone Project 1 - a Static Website

- Creating a static website showcasing my portfolio

- tools I used:
- Git
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap 4

■ Data Miner/Marketer

United States Patent and Trademark Office (USPTO)
May 2020 - Present (2 years 2 months +)

Education

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp

Postgraduate/ Certificate Course, Fullstack Web Development 2022 - 2022

STI College

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology Jul 2018 - Mar 2020

Licenses & Certifications

- Fullstack Web Development Zuitt Coding Bootcamp https://share.zertify.zuitt.co/certificate/4814fb2a-51f7-408d-b796-44082fcdfe35
- Backend Web Development Zuitt Coding Bootcamp https://share.zertify.zuitt.co/certificate/8c2a407b-c535-496a-aadd-9ce8eaef729f
- Microsoft Professional Program in Front-End Web Development Zuitt Coding Bootcamp

https://share.zertify.zuitt.co/certificate/e792e78c-c726-4bd2-aa9d-e90617d4a4f2

Skills

JavaScript • Express.js • React.js • Node.js • MongoDB • Full-Stack Development • Front-End Development • Back-End Web Development